{
  "type": "writing",
  "language_code": "zh-CN",
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "Wèi",
      "answer": "位"
    },
    {
      "question": "Chē",
      "answer": "车"
    },
    {
      "question": "Diànnǎo",
      "answer": "电脑"
    },
    {
      "question": "Cídiǎn",
      "answer": "词典"
    },
    {
      "question": "Háizi",
      "answer": "孩子"
    },
    {
      "question": "Zhùjiào",
      "answer": "助教"
    },
    {
      "question": "Xì zhǔrèn",
      "answer": "系主任"
    },
    {
      "question": "Lǜshī",
      "answer": "律师"
    },
    {
      "question": "Gōngchéngshī",
      "answer": "工程师"
    },
    {
      "question": "Yéyé",
      "answer": "爷爷"
    },
    {
      "question": "Wàigōng",
      "answer": "外公"
    },
    {
      "question": "Nián",
      "answer": "年"
    },
    {
      "question": "Qián",
      "answer": "前"
    },
    {
      "question": "Chángcháng",
      "answer": "常常"
    },
  ]
}
